infoproductkiller.com 2012-12-27

# InfoProductKiller.com - Privacy Policy

## INTRODUCTION

### Purpose of Policy

Untapped Limited (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, affiliates and other users of the Company’s family of websites (the “Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.

### Notice Concerning Children

We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children. If you are under 18 years of age (21 years of age where 18 is not the age of majority), you may only use the Site with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

The information we learn from visitors helps us personalize and continually improve your experience on the Site. We use the information to handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us, display content such as websites we host for you, and recommend products and services that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve our Site, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Site and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

### What Types of Information do We Collect?

Anonymous Traffic Data. We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: IP addresses; domain servers; types of computers accessing the Site; and types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We also use “cookies” to customize content specific to you and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site.

Personal Information You Provide to Us. In order for you to access certain premium, services and to purchase products that we offer via the Site, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (i) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, and e-mail address); (ii) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number); and (iii) Demographic Data (such as your zip code and age). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

Information from Other Sources. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

### What About Cookies?

We may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer to enable our system to recognize your browser and to provide customized features when you return to our Site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

## USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

### What Do We Do With Collected Information?

Company Use of Information. We use Contact Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We use your Financial Data to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and to bill you for products and services.

### Do We Share the Information We Receive?

Information about our customers, visitors, affiliates and other users is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share certain categories of information we collect from you only in the ways described in this Privacy Policy.

Anonymous Information. We may share Demographic Data with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis.

Promotional Offers. We may share Contact Data with other companies who may want to send you information about their products or services, but only if you have specifically requested that we share Contact Data with such companies. These companies must have agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy prior to receiving your Personal Information.

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control. We work closely with certain other businesses. In some cases, we sell product and/or service lines jointly with or on behalf of these businesses. We share Personal Information related to those transactions with that third party.

Third Party Service Providers. We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. They have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the Personal Information in accordance with this Policy and as permitted by the UK's Data Protection Act.

Disclosure of Personal Information. We may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Company or its affiliates, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Company or the users of the Site, (iii) enforce an agreement between you and us, or (iv) to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site in exigent circumstances.

Business Transfers. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Policy. If Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

Compliance with Data Protection Laws. Whenever we transfer Personal Information to countries outside of the European Economic Area in the course of sharing information as set out above, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Policy and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection.

### Your Access and Control of Your Personal Information

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you may still be able to access some portions of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your registration.

We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may visit your personal profile within the My Account area of the Software Site. Through your personal profile you may: (i) review and update your Personal Information that we have already collected; (ii) choose whether or not you wish us to send you information about our company, or promotional material from some of our partners; and/or (iii) choose whether or not you wish for us to share your Personal Information with third parties.

## SECURITY

The Site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Personal Information that we obtain from you. Our Site, like all websites, may be subject to hacking, malicious acts and other events that compromise the security of your Personal Information. As such, we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.. You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, user name, or password from your account and update our records accordingly.

## SITE AREAS BEYOND OUR CONTROL

### Public Forums

We may make interactive forums, message boards, chat rooms and news groups available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your information.

### Third Party Websites

The Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. It is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

## CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to the Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel contact us at the following e-mail address: privacy (-at-) untappedseo.com

### Updates and Changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
